(Penny:)What? Are you kidding?
We're not hanging it!
(Leonard:)But it's an expression
of our love.
And our butts!
Not hanging it!
(Leonard:)Seems a shame to throw it away.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(gasps)
(Penny:)We could give it to Sheldon,
(Penny:)and tell him William
Shatner painted it.
(Leonard:)God, I love you.
I love you so much.
(Amy:)I think I'm gonna go home.
(Penny:)Why?
(Sheldon:)I really don't understand
what's happening here.
(Amy:)You know, Sheldon,
at any other time,
(Amy:)learning that you had plans
to go live on Mars
(Amy:)would be a slow news day.
(Amy:)But a couple of hours ago,
(Amy:)we were getting a turtle.
(Amy:)And silly as it sounds,
(Amy:)I thought that meant something.
Amy!
(Sheldon:)Oh, why didn't I give her
Sleepy Time tea?